原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     灰灰是菇涼  獨醉  油膩希
校對     某賽出門灰灰代班
后期      灰灰是菇涼      時間軸    加森
總監     新浪微博@賽太公
生
活
大
爆
炸
第十二季  第三集
佩妮  我們跟鄰居聊天
So, Penny, we were talking to our neighbors,
他們說在考慮賣掉房子搬家
and they're thinking of moving and selling their house.
真的嗎  為什么
Really? Why?
好像跟孩子哭鬧
Something about babies crying
整晚睡不好覺有關  原因不重要
and keeping them up all night; it's not important.
你們倆應該考慮下要不要買
You guys should totally take a look at it.
那樣我們就可以做鄰居了
Then we could be neighbors.
慢著  那我們呢
Hey. Wait a minute, what about us?
我們現在結婚了
I mean, we're married now.
也許我們想買到你們隔壁呢
Maybe we want to buy the house next door.
艾米  我們可不能搬家
Well, Amy, we can't move.
不然我就得換掉我內褲上的所有標簽了
I'd have to change all the tags in my underwear.
你可以買新的
You can buy new ones.
什么  換新房子  還要換新內褲  怎么
What-- new house, new underwear. What am I,
美國聯邦司法部管理的證人保護項目
為受到威脅的證人提供新身份與住所
我是進了證人保護計劃嗎
in the Witness Protection Program?
好吧  你們怎么想
Okay. Guys, so what do you think?
我說不好  我們在這里住得挺好
Well, I don't know, w-we're pretty happy here.
對  再說  要是我們想搬家
Yeah. Plus, if we moved,
可能會去市區找一間躍層式公寓
we'd probably just get a loft downtown.
真的嗎
Really?
我一直以為我們會找個帶院子的房子
I always figured we'd get a place with a yard.
行吧  這就說得通了
Oh, sure, yeah, that makes sense,
那你就可以去投籃和修剪草坪了
so you could shoot hoops and mow the lawn?
你倆是怎么結婚的
How are you two married?
你當時在場  我磨得她煩了不得不嫁
You were there. I wore her down.
沒錯
He did.
你們應該在約會的時候
You guys should've talked about all this stuff
就把這些都聊明白
while you were dating.
我和安奴就已經對彼此了如指掌了
I mean, me and Anu already know so much about each other.
慢著  我忘了  安奴是你的脫毛師嗎
Wait, I forget, is Anu your waxer?
不是  那是安妮特
Uh, no, that's Annette.
安奴是我爸給我介紹的相親對象
Anu is the woman my father fixed me up with.
明天我們就要第一次約會了
We're going on our first date tomorrow.
這提醒了我  我得找安妮特脫個毛
Which reminds me, I need to see Annette.
你真的讓你父親來給你挑選妻子嗎
You're really letting your father pick out a wife?
為什么要拒絕
Why not?
包辦婚姻已經延續上千年了
Arranged marriages have been working for thousands of years.
我和安奴出身相仿
Anu and I come from similar backgrounds,
我們的家庭交好
our families get along
我們還各自填了問卷
and we each filled out questionnaires,
這樣就不會把時間浪費在
so we know we're not wasting our time
跟你不匹配的人身上
with someone who's not compatible.
這也太枯燥死板了吧
Oh, that sounds so dry and clinical.
你這個幸運的小子
You lucky duck.
我只是覺得沒有有對方相處過
I just don't think you can truly know someone
是無法真正了解一個人的
until you've spent a lot of time with them.
真的嗎  那佩妮夢想的度假地是哪里
Really? What's Penny's dream vacation?
馬里布海景別墅
Malibu beach house.
那是芭比娃娃的夢想度假地
That's Barbie's dream vacation.
不如你把問卷發給我們吧
Maybe you should send us that questionnaire.
讀書還開心嗎
Enjoying your book?
開心得要死
So much.
你為什么要一直在書上戳戳戳
Why do you keep poking at it?
被你發現了  我在手機上購物
Fine, I'm shopping on my phone.
是你說要多讀點書的
You're the one who said you wanted to read more.
對  我還告訴別人我只給孩子吃有機食品呢
Yes, I also tell people I only feed the kids organic.
隨口一說罷了
It's just stuff you say.
好啊
Hello.
玩兒得開心嗎
How was your night?
挺棒的  我們去看即興表演了
Ah, it was great. We went to an improv show.
他們要觀眾提一個詞來表演
Yeah. They asked the audience to suggest a word,
最后用了斯圖爾特的
and they used Stuart's.
棒  什么詞
Oh, cool, what was it?
椰子
Coconuts.
這詞太妙了
It was such a good one.
我靈機一動
It just came to me.
-你們倆在干什么  -讀書
- Uh, what are you guys up to? - Reading.
真好  我也希望能多讀點書
Oh, nice, I wish I read more.
如果讀書對你很重要  那你總能擠出時間的
Well, if it's important, you find the time.
你想參觀下我的房間嗎
You want to see my room?
-好  -好極了
-Yeah. -‭Cool.
你什么感覺
How do you feel about this?
她顯然能找個更好的  不過我沒發言資格
That she can clearly do better, but that's not for me to say.
不  我是說他們在里面干什么呢
No, with them in his room, doing stuff.
不會的  我們就坐在外面
Oh, come on, we're sitting right out here.
他們不會做什么的
They're not gonna do anything.
我想更改答案
I'd like to change my answer.
你真的很擅長涂指甲
Wow, you really are good at this.
我可是用了大把時間給模型上色的人
Well, I've spent a lot of time painting D&D miniatures.
我知道你為此欲火焚身想扒了我的衣服
I know that makes you want to rip my shirt off,
不過先等指甲干了吧
but wait until your nails are dry.
是拉杰
Oh, it's Raj.
他把那份印度婚姻問卷發來了
He sent us that Indian marriage questionnaire.
-快念念  -好
- Ooh, read one. ‭- Okay.
你對宗教有多虔誠
"How religious are you?"
這個簡單  我倆都不信教
That's easy, both of us: not at all.
不  我不是一點都不信
No, I wouldn't say not at all.
我對精神洗滌很感興趣
I mean, I am pretty spiritual.
我會去做瑜伽  所以...
I do go to yoga, so...
好  那你的教堂就是女士彈力褲
Great, so your church is Our Lady of the Stretchy Pants.
下一個問題
Next question.
你和家人有多親密
Uh, "How close are you with your family?"
很親
Pretty close.
我覺得我家不是很親
I'm gonna say not too close,
我希望再疏遠些
but I'm hoping to get farther.
你對孩子有什么看法
How do you feel about children?
還行吧
Um, they're okay, I guess.
我看到孩子不會對著他扔石頭的
I mean, if I saw one, I wouldn't throw a rock at it.
你為什么要對一個孩子扔石頭
W-Why would you throw a rock at a child?
我說了我不會扔
I just said I wouldn't.
這問題是問你想不想要孩子
The question is would you like to have kids.
答案是肯定的  我們想要孩子
So, yeah, we want kids.
好吧  以后會有的
Yeah-- someday.
嗯  五年內吧
Right, like, in the next five years.
行吧  下一個問題
Sure, uh, next question.
你跟寵物相處得好嗎
"How are you with pets?"
我照顧了謝爾頓十五年
Well, I did take care of Sheldon for 15 years,
他只咬過我兩次
and he only bit me twice.
在讀了你填的問卷以后  我得說
I have to say, uh, after reading your questionnaire,
我感覺已經很了解你了
I feel like I already know you.
沒錯  我也這么覺得  服務員
Totally. Me, too. Excuse me.
把水換成起泡酒
Can we please get sparkling instead of tap,
上點擦亮的銀器餐具  再看看他們在吃什么
some clean silverware and find out what they're having?
看起來很美味
That looks delicious.
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
謝謝
Thank you.
這么說  你是天文物理學家
So, you're an astrophysicist.
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
我  我是說  是的
I-I mean, uh, just yes.
除非你想要我稱你為"女士"
U-Unless you prefer "Ma'am."
不必了
I don't.
好  因為你不像一位高傲的女士
‭Good, because you don't seem like a ma'am.
而是一個小甜心
You seem more like a sweet thang.
你真的對撩妹一竅不通
You are not good at this.
要是我懂怎么撩妹
Well, if I was good at this,
又何必讓我爸來給我安排相親
I wouldn't need to be fixed up by my father.
我也從沒想過我會接受家里的安排
I never thought I'd let my family set me up, either,
可我已經34歲了  我想要孩子
but I'm 34, I'd like to have kids
但我工作太忙沒時間約會
and it's hard to date because I work so much.
對了  你是酒店禮賓
Oh, yes, uh, you're a concierge.
暫時是這樣  我打算五年內自己經營一家酒店
For now. I plan to be managing a hotel in the next five years.
要是能把現在的老板踢走  四年就能搞定
Four, if I can get the current manager out of the way.
他是個煙鬼  祝他好運
He's a smoker, so fingers crossed.
我明白  你知道嗎  我以前給未來的妻子
I-I get it. You know, um, I used to have a long list
列過一長串的要求
of what I wanted from a wife.
美國女演員  一頭濃密棕發  曾憑影片《弱點》獲奧斯卡最佳女主
要有桑德拉·布洛克那樣的眼睛
Uh, eyes like Sandra Bullock,
桑德拉·布洛克那樣的秀發
hair like Sandra Bullock,
還要有瑞安·斯通那樣的勇氣
and the bravery of Ryan Stone.
那是桑德拉·布洛克在《地心引力》里的角色
That's Sandra Bullock's character in Gravity.
不過現在
But now,
我只希望遇到一個性格好的
I-I just want someone nice.
我覺得我性格很好  你呢
I think I'm nice. Are you nice?
我性格可好了
Oh, I'm definitely nice.
每次有姑娘跟我分手  說的第一句話都是
Every time a girl breaks up with me she always starts with,
"你是個好人"
"You're a nice guy."
聽著  你很貼心
Look, your whole sweet,
你的不自信也很可愛
insecure thing is cute,
但說實話  我沒那么多閑工夫
but honestly, I have no time for that.
如果你不是認真的
If you're not serious about this,
現在就走人
you need to walk away now.
我是認真的
I-I am serious.
很好
Good.
好的
Okay.
好的  這是什么意思
O-Okay, w-what does this mean?
意思就是我可能是未來的...
I think it means I might be the future Mrs....
庫薩帕里夫人
Koothrappali.
如果我不跟夫姓  你會有何感想
How would you feel if I didn't change my name?
有點受傷  但我不會告訴你  因為我是大好人
A little hurt, but you wouldn't know, because I'm too nice.
想去吃午餐嗎
Hey, want to get lunch?
不行
I can't.
哈雷和邁克爾整晚沒睡  我的進度完全落后了
Halley and Michael were up all night, and I'm way behind here.
-他們病了嗎  -不是
- Oh, no, are they sick? - ‭No.
他們只是像兩個小混蛋一樣邊笑邊玩
They were just laughing and playing like a couple of jerks.
他們是很可愛  但什么都被他們毀了
Boy, they're cute, but they ruin everything.
我明白
I get that.
最近我一直在想
You know, I've been thinking lately
也許我不想要孩子
that maybe I don't want kids.
你瘋了嗎
Are you crazy?
你當然要生孩子  他們棒呆了
Of course you want them. It's amazing.
你剛說什么都被他們毀了
You just said they ruin everything.
我有權利這樣說  我笑的時候漏尿是他們的錯
I'm allowed to. It's their fault I pee when I laugh.
等等   為什么我說
Hang on, why is it crazy
不想要孩子就是瘋了
to say I might not want kids?
不是瘋了
Oh, it's not crazy.
只是錯了
It's just wrong.
你只是現在想著你不要孩子
You only think you don't want kids,
但你一旦生了孩子  你會發現其實你是想要孩子的
but once you have kids, you'll realize that you did want them.
又或者我不要孩子  我就不會生孩子  你別管我
Or I don't want them, so I won't have them, so back off.
你這口氣真像我還沒有成為母親
Aw, you sound just like me before I became a mom
沒有領悟愛的真諦的時候
and learned what the meaning of love was.
不敢相信你居然一副高高在上的樣子
Wow, I cannot believe how condescending you're being.
我知道很嚇人  但你會成為很好的母親
Look, I know it's scary, but you're gonna be a great mom.
我知道  但重點是我不想當媽
I know I'd be great, but the point is I don't want to be one.
也許你當不了一個好母親  你的脾氣太爆
Maybe you wouldn't be great. You kind of got a temper.
不是所有人都需要孩子來實現人生價值
You know, not everyone needs to have kids to be fulfilled.
你說得對  你有萊納德了
You're right, you've got Leonard.
還需要什么孩子呢
What more do you need?
-各位  -你好
- Hey, guys. - Hello. ‭
約會怎么樣
How was your date?
讓我用一個問題來回答
Ah, let me answer that with a question.
你愿意做我的伴郎嗎
How would you like to be my best man?
慢著  你不會真要娶一個
Wait, you're not seriously
只見過一次的女人吧
marrying a woman you've met once.
有何不可  她人很好  我人很好
Why not? She's nice, I'm nice.
我們有可能會和其他夫妻一樣幸福
We're just as likely to be happy as any other two people.
也許更幸福
Maybe even happier.
抱歉  我沒有針對你
Sorry, that was not a swipe at you.
我本來沒覺得你針對我
I didn't think it was.
很好  因為我沒有
Yeah, good, 'cause it was not.
我個人來說
Well, I, for one,
為拉杰的決定喝彩  他放棄了感情束縛
applaud Raj's decision to forgo emotional attachment
通過屈服于三千年的獨裁傳統
and find a life partner by bowing
找到了人生伴侶
to a 3,000-year-old authoritarian tradition.
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
你娶了自己愛的女人
You married a woman you're in love with.
我不敢相信你用這件事回擊我
I can't believe you're throwing that back in my face.
你為什么不能為我開心
Why can't you just be happy for me?
因為你這樣很傻
Because you're being dumb.
你對她一點也不了解
You don't know anything about her.
憑什么你們都結婚了
W-Well, how come you all get to be married
就我一個人單身
and I have to stay single?
這問題恐怕要專業的心理咨詢師才能回答
I think that's a question for a licensed professional.
知道嗎  你不僅羞辱了我
You know what, you're not just insulting me.
你還羞辱了我的家人  我的文化
Okay? You're insulting my family, my culture
和我未來的新娘安努
and my future bride, Anu,
她是畢業于康奈爾大學的碩士  她吃素
a vegetarian with a master's degree from Cornell
最愛的水果是菠蘿
whose favorite fruit is pineapple.
我不確定這話是否有幫助  但你們知道嗎
Now, I'm not sure if this helps, but did you know
菠蘿曾經非常稀有
that pineapples were once so rare
查爾斯國王找人繪制肖像時曾讓菠蘿一起入畫
that King Charles posed for a portrait with one?
這話能有什么幫助
How does that help?
幫了我  幾年來我一直設法
Oh, it helped me. I've been trying to slide that
在聊天中提起這事
into a conversation for years.
親愛的  今天過得好嗎
Hey, honey, how was your day?
怎么了
What's wrong?
拉杰說
Raj is talking about
要娶他剛認識的女人
marrying this woman he just met.
我說這樣做很傻  現在他生我氣了
I told him it was dumb, and now he's mad at me.
我有同樣的遭遇
The same thing happened to me.
佩妮說她不想要孩子
Penny said she didn't want kids,
我說她這樣很傻
and I told her she was being silly,
她指責我高高在上
and she accused me of being condescending.
真是瘋了  如果我想要高高在上
Which is crazy, because if I wanted to be condescending,
我會說  啊  你居然會用
I would've said, "Ooh, 'condescending.'
"高高在上"這么高級的詞
That's such a big word."
我們的朋友為什么不聽我們的勸
Why won't our friends just listen to us?
顯然我們是有經驗的
We obviously know what we're talking about.
我知道
I know.
我們結婚了  我們有很好的孩子
We're married, we have great kids,
很好的工作  很好的房子
great jobs, this great house.
萊納德  還記得昨天
Hey, Leonard, remember yesterday
-我們說以后會生孩子嗎  -怎么了
- when we were talking about having kids someday? - Yeah?
如果不是以后呢
Well, what if it wasn't someday.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我的天  你懷孕了嗎
Oh, my God, are you pregnant?
沒沒沒  沒有  絕對沒有
No. No. No, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
那...
So?
沒有
No. ‭
我意思是
What I meant was,
如果我們不要孩子呢
what if, what if we didn't have kids?
永遠不要嗎
Ever?
我們的生活這么幸福
I mean, our life is so great.
為什么要改變呢
Why would we want to change that?
當然  當然
Sure. Sure.
當然
Sure.
我想在你從沒告訴過我的
And I guess it would be hard raising kids
你想要的躍層式公寓里養孩子是挺難的
in the-the loft you never told me you wanted.
-等等  別生氣  -我沒生氣
- Well, wait, don't be mad. - I'm not mad.
我為什么要生氣
Why would I be mad?
根本沒什么可生氣的
There's nothing to be mad at!
你得轉一下那個
You have to-to turn the thing.
我知道
I knew that!
-萊納德  -我沒生氣
- Hi, Leonard. - I'm not mad!
你安靜得出奇
You're awfully quiet.
-抱歉  -不  我喜歡
- Sorry. - No, I like it.
我有很多煩心事
Got a lot on my mind.
你想談談嗎
Would you like to talk about it?
不想
Not really.
早餐吃全谷麥片  安靜的行車旅程
Grape Nuts for breakfast, quiet car ride,
我今天真是事事順心
things are really breaking my way today.
佩妮的重大消息殺了我一個措手不及
It's just Penny hit me with some pretty big news
要消化的東西太多了
and it's a lot to process.
你想安靜地消化  我尊重你
And you'd like to do that quietly. I respect that.
她說她不想要孩子
She said she doesn't want to have kids.
也許她不是認真的
Maybe she didn't mean it,
就像你說你不想談這事
like when you said you didn't want to talk about this.
算了
Forget it.
你想要孩子嗎
Do you want to have children?
我一直以為以后會有的  但現在我發現
Well, I always assumed we would and now I find out, you know,
霍夫斯塔德一家到我這可能就絕子絕孫了
I might be the last of the Hofstadter line.
你哥不是有孩子嗎
Doesn't your brother have children?
還有你姐  她保留了娘家姓
And your sister. She kept the Hofstadter name
生了五個健康的兒子
and has five healthy boys:
尼爾  杰弗里  斯科特  威廉  還有理查德寶寶
Neil, Jeffrey, Scott, William and baby Richard.
我還是繼續安靜吧
I'm going back to being quiet.
太好了
Sweet.
我能坐下嗎
Hey. Mind if I sit?
你是來告訴我  我犯下了天大的錯誤嗎
Did you just come here to tell me I'm making a gigantic mistake
因為我點了藍莓松餅
by having this blueberry muffin
我應該像你一樣吃肉桂卷
and I should've got a cinnamon roll like you did?
不是
No.
那就好  因為我對自己的選擇很滿意
Good, 'cause I'm happy with my choice.
不過那個肉桂卷確實挺香的
Although that cinnamon roll does smell good
你能分我一半嗎
if you're open to halfsies.
-行吧  -謝謝
- Fine. ‭- Thanks.
昨天的事我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry about yesterday.
你說得對  我當時太...
You're right. I-I was being...
我的老天鵝  太好吃了
Oh, my God, that is so good!
等會再說吧
I can wait.
不  抱歉
No... Sorry.
你繼續
Go on.
我們認識很久了
I've known you a long time.
你是我見過的最相信浪漫的人
You believe in romance more than any person I've ever met
看到你放棄  我很難受
and it's hard to see you give up on that.
但如果你真覺得跟這個女人結婚
But if you really think marrying this woman
能讓你快樂
is gonna make you happy,
那我全心全意支持你
then you have my complete and total support.
我會陪你走過每一步
I will be with you every step of the way.
謝謝  霍華德  這番話意義重大
Thanks, Howard. That means a lot.
那婚禮會在印度舉行嗎
So, hey, is this wedding gonna be in India?
有可能哦
Ah, maybe.
搞毛啊  佩妮
What the hell, Penny?!
你得說具體一點我才知道
I'm gonna need more than that.
你不打算生孩子
You're not having kids?
你怎么能這樣對我
How could you do this to me?
這關你什么事啊
How is it any of your business?
因為你的小孩本該當我家小孩的朋友
Because your kids were supposed to be friends with my kids.
現在誰來當他們的朋友
Who's gonna be friends with them now?
他們會交到其他朋友啊
They will find other friends.
當然了  因為擁有我和謝爾頓基因的小孩
Oh, sure, 'cause Sheldon's DNA plus my DNA
一定八面玲瓏很會交朋友  成熟一點
equals a kid who knows how to make friends. Grow up!
這是我和萊納德兩個人的事
This is between me and Leonard.
萊納德吃屎吧  我們本該一起懷孕
Screw Leonard! We were supposed to get pregnant together.
一起孕吐
We were gonna be barf buddies.
并用維他命E幫對方
We were supposed to massage each other's perineums
按摩會陰
with vitamin E.
你現在就快把我說吐了
I'm about to be your barf buddy right now.
聽著  你有小孩后
Listen, when you have kids,
我還是會陪在你身邊
I'm still gonna be there.
我會是他們好玩的佩妮阿姨  給他們糖吃
I'm gonna be their fun Aunt Penny who gives them candy,
教他們罵臟話
and teaches them swear words
還會跟他們說媽媽有多奇葩
and tells them stories about what a weirdo their mother is.
這我應該能接受
I guess I could live with that.
真正艱難的是放棄我們
What is gonna be hard is letting go of the dream
用母乳喂養彼此小孩的夢想
of us breastfeeding each other's babies.
忘記你說過這段話也很艱難
And it's gonna be hard to forget you said that.
拒絕
No.
要是我說浴袍底下的我
What would you say if I told you
一絲不掛  你有什么想法
I was totally naked under this robe?
我會覺得還不錯
I would say that sounds pretty good.
真的嗎  還真沒料到
Really? Well, I did not see that coming.
馬上就好
One second.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
等等  別被嚇軟
Wait. Stay in the mood.
我來放我們的音樂  蓋過他們
I'll put on our own music and drown them out.
小甜甜布蘭妮熱單《Work Bitch》
這是什么
What's this?
我健身專用的合集
It's from my workout mix.
我鍛煉臀大肌時就聽這首歌
It's what I listen to when I'm firming up my glutes.
你去看看他吧
Can you get him?
好
Sure.
-霍華德  -干嘛
- Hey, Howard. - ‭Yeah?
你緊實的臀大肌看起來能夾爆核桃
It looks like you could crack a walnut in those glutes.
不行  我試過了
I can't. I tried.
我給你做了晚飯
I-I made you dinner.
你的最愛  快餐店買的漢堡拆了包裝用盤子裝起來
Your favorite: In-N-Out Burger out of the wrapper on a plate.
謝謝  但你不必這么做  我沒事
Thank you, but you don't have to do this. I'm fine.
我知道這不是嬰兒  但被捧起時它也會漏汁[尿]哦
I-I know it's not a baby, but it does leak when you pick it up.
你不是吧  現在還拿這個開玩笑了
Really? We're joking about this now?
不是的  對不起
No, look, I'm sorry.
我不是有意這么突然就告訴你的
I didn't mean to just drop all of this on you.
我只是很驚訝
I-It just took me by surprise.
我以前常想象生孩子的事
I-I always imagined having kids.
我知道
I know you did.
但我想象過很多
But I've imagined having a lot of things
我永遠也得不到的東西
that I'm never gonna get:
《蝙蝠俠》中的高科技戰車
諾貝爾獎  能開的蝙蝠戰車a Nobel Prize, a working Batmobile.
但我也擁有很多從沒想過能得到的事物
But I also have a lot that I never thought I'd have...
比如你
like you.
你確定這就足夠了嗎
Are you sure that's enough?
是的
Yeah.
-你真能接受這個決定  -是的
- You're really okay with this? - ‭I am.
爸爸
Hey, Daddy.
萊納德說
What's this Leonard says
你不想給我生外孫  怎么回事
about you not wanting to give me grandbabies?
他可能有其他想法  先閃了
He might feel differently. Bye.
我告訴爸媽我們第一次約會很順利
I told my parents our first date went well
他們很興奮
and they got very excited.
可不是嘛
Oh, tell me about it.
我爸媽也高興壞了
My parents were so thrilled,
他們竟然跟對方說話了
they actually spoke to each other.
那結局并不美好
So that was a disaster.
干杯
Cheers.
好了  如果我們要舉行婚禮
Okay. I guess if we're going forward with this wedding,
現在該討論接下來的步驟了
we should talk about the next steps.
你是指婚禮主題和用哪些花嗎
Oh, like themes and flowers?
其實是財務和稅務
Actually, finances and taxes.
我們不能用這個
Oh. We can't use that.
這是我爸媽的離婚主題
That was the theme of my parents' divorce.
我知道錢可能會使新婚夫婦
I know that money can be a source of friction
產生摩擦  我希望能避免這一點
in a new marriage and I want us to avoid that.
當然了  對
Of course. Yeah, right.
這樣很明智
That's s-smart.
我的會計強烈建議
So, my accountant feels strongly
我們婚后第一年分別報稅
that we should file separately the first year
之后再根據我們的共同資產重新評估
and then we can re-evaluate based on our joint assets.
你還好嗎
You okay?
我不能這么做
No, I can't do this.
為什么
Why not?
我有些方面你可能不太了解
Th-There's something you may not know about me
因為我們只見過一次面  但是
'cause, you know, we've only met once, but...
我浪漫得不可救藥
I'm a hopeless romantic.
你看起來很優秀
And you seem great
我也確實想結婚
and I do want to get married.
想定下來  但是
I-I do want to settle down, but...
這不是我以后想告訴孫輩的愛情故事
this isn't the story that I want to tell my grandkids.
我懂
I understand.
要是浪費你時間了  我很抱歉
I'm so sorry if I wasted your time.
拉杰
Raj.
我知道我們彼此不太了解
I know we don't know each other very well,
但你看起來會是個好父親
but you seem like you'd make a good father
而且你夠高  我不怕穿上高跟鞋會比你高
and you're tall enough so I can wear heels and...
我認為這就值得我們為之努力了
I think that's something worth fighting for.
你愿意娶我嗎
Will you marry me?
天啊天啊天啊
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
當然愿意  我當然愿意娶你
Yes, of course, of course I'll marry you!
-你想的話可以吻我  -太好了
- If you'd like to kiss me you can. - ‭Oh, great.
先提醒你一下  我有舌釘
I should warn you I have a tongue piercing.
你也沒那么乖嘛
Oh, you're not that nice.
你要告訴我這是去哪兒嗎
Are you gonna tell me where we're going?
因為如果目的地有"農貿"或"市場"這幾個字
Because if it has the words "Farmers" or "Market" in it,
我不想去
I don't want to go.
你之前說到有些事物
You were talking about all the things
你認為自己永遠都得不到
you thought you would never have,
所以我就送你一樣
so I thought I would get you one.
老天啊  你買了蝙蝠戰車給我
Oh, my God. You bought me the Batmobile?!
不是
No. No.
我不是我沒有
No, no, no, no, no.
我給你租了一天的蝙蝠戰車
I rented you the Batmobile for the day.
這太棒了  謝謝你
This is amazing. Thank you.
小心點  我沒買保險
B-Be careful. I-I did not get the insurance.
快上來  羅賓
Come on, Robin!